<resources>
<string name="app_name">Uncle Finney\'s Poker</string>
<string name="app_uri">finneypoker.liveplayergames.com</string>
<string name="player_server">http://finneypoker.liveplayergames.com:3000</string>
<string name="contract_addr">0xff1f9c77a0f1fd8f48cfeee58b714ca03420ddac</string>
<string name="welcome">
Uncle Finney\'s Poker is a two-player contest. When you register with our server,
the game will create a Finney wallet for you. Before each contest, you and your chosen
opponent agree on the maximum size of each poker bet (in \"Finney\").
\n\nOnce you have agreed on a maximum bet size, the game-app will deposit an ante equal
to one quarter of the maximum bet, in a secure, 3rd-party blockchain contract. Similarly,
each time you bet, you will send your funds to that 3rd-party contract.
\n\nOnce there is a declared winner of the contest, the blockchain contract will return
the total pot amount (minus processing fees) to the winner. If there is no winner, for
example in the highly unlikely case of a game-server crash, or in case the
internet connection cuts out before the game begins, then the funds are returned to both
players.
\n\nNote: Your Finney wallet is maintained entirely on your phone &#8212; our servers do
not have access to your Finneys. The game server only matches you up with an opponent.
The game server and its authors have no way to withdraw the wager
funds &#8212; we can only inform the contract about who is the winner.
\n\nYou can transfer your Finney from your wallet to other players directly, using the
Send-or-Receive-Finney page.
\n\nWARNING: CITIZENS AND RESIDENTS OF THE UNITED STATES AND OTHER COUNTRIES IN WHICH
THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE MIGHT BE ILLIGAL ARE HEREBY PROHIBITED FROM USING THIS SOFTWARE.
\n\nEnjoy!
</string>
  <string name="welcome_help_title">
About Your Balance
</string>
  <string name="welcome_help">
The balance displayed on this screen, when up-to-date, reflects your current balance
on the blockchain. It does not include transactions that have not yet been accepted
on the blockchain, which can take up to 5 minutes, depending on network conditions. For
this reason, the balance, even when synced with the blockchain, may not reflect winnings
from your most recent game for a few minutes.
</string>
<string name="device_id_title">
We Need to Know Your Phone Device-id
</string>
<string name="device_id_rationale">
We need to access your phone state in order to register you as a unique player in
our system. We only use your device id; but we are required to ask your permission
for this. On the next screen we will ask for permission to access your phone info.
Note: Unfortunately, on some phones the system permission to access the device information
is bundled with the permission to make calls. We will not make any calls.
</string>
  <string name="enter_username_title">
Enter a Username
</string>
  <string name="enter_username">
Enter a username by which you will be known to other players:
</string>
  <string name="username_taken">
The username that you entered is already taken by a different player. Please
enter a different username by which you will be known to other players:
</string>
  <string name="giveaway_title">
Finney Giveaway!
</string>
  <string name="giveaway">
To encourage more people to try Uncle Finney\'s Poker, sometimes we
\n\nGIVE AWAY FREE FINNEY!
\n\nWe have sent you FINNEY_AMOUNT Finney REASON
\n\nThe funds will appear in your account within a minute or so.
\n\nThanks for using Uncle Finney\'s Poker!
</string>
<string name="motd_title">
Note:
</string>
  <string name="registering_username">
Registering your username&#8230;
</string>
  <string name="no_acct">
You have not set up a Finney (Ether) account yet. Before using this app you need
to import an Ether account using the "import account" menu item.
</string>
<string name="share_subtitle">
Finney Wallet
</string>
<!-- subtitle in option bar for receive activity. receive activity is laos used to show qr
  code for export acct -->
<string name="receive_subtitle_receive">
Receive Payment
</string>
<string name="receive_subtitle_export">
Export Account
</string>
<string name="receive_err_no_media_access_msg">
Unable to access media directory
</string>
<string name="receive_err_no_media_access_permission">
We cannot share unless you provide access to external storage
</string>
  <!-- subtitle in option bar for scan, send activities. for scan subtitle depends on what we are scanning... -->
<string name="subtitle_send">
Send Payment"
</string>
<string name="subtitle_import">
Import Account
</string>
<string name="cant_scan_cuz_no_access_msg">
We cannot scan because we do not have permission to access the camera.
</string>
<string name="scan_addr_prompt">
Scan the QR code that represents the recipient address. Once the recipient
address has been identified, you will be able to specify the amount of Finney
(Ether) that you would like to send.
</string>
<string name="scan_key_prompt">
Scan the QR code that represents the private key for the account that you want
to import.
\n\nHint: To get a QR code for the private key for your account, you can visit
https://www.myetherwallet.com and select the view-wallet-info tab.
</string>
<string name="ask_delete_old_key">
Uncle Finney\'s Poker only supports a single account. If you import a new
account, then you erase your current account &#8212; (the account still exists,
of course, but you will not be able to access it from Uncle Finney\'s-Poker.)
\n\nIMPORTANT: if you have any funds in this account, and if you don\'t have
access to the account from some other wallet, then you should transfer the funds
before you import a new account. Otherwise you will lose your funds!
</string>

  <!-- transaction list and payment processor -->
  <string name="txid">txid</string>
  <string name="from">from</string>
  <string name="to">to</string>
  <string name="balance">balance</string>
  <string name="encrypting">encrypting</string>
  <string name="encrypt_err">error encoding transaction!</string>
  <string name="continuing_refresh">continuing refresh</string>
  <string name="waiting_for_nonce">waiting_for_nonce</string>
  <string name="refreshing_nonce">refreshing account status (nonce)&#8230;</string>
  <string name="refreshing_price">refreshing account status (price)&#8230;</string>
  <string name="refreshing_balance">refreshing account status (balance)&#8230;</string>

  <!-- purchase messages -->
<string name="purchase_subtitle">Purchase Finney</string>
<string name="retrieving_price_list">retrieving price list</string>
<string name="payment_declined">payment was declined</string>
<string name="forwarding_payment_confirmation">forwarding payment confirmation</string>
<string name="payment_cancelled">payment was canceled</string>
<string name="payment_not_valid">payment was not valid</string>
<string name="failed_to_retrieve_price_list">failed to retrieve price list</string>
<string name="error_parsing_price_list">error parsing price list</string>
<string name="Server_Error">Server Error</string>
<string name="purchase_complete_title">Purchase Complete</string>
<string name="purchase_complete_msg">
Your purchase completed successfully. Please allow one or two minutes for your new Finney to be credited to your account
</string>
<string name="purchase_err_title">Unable to Complete Purchase</string>
<string name="purchase_err_msg">
An error was encountered while processing your purchase:
\n\nSTATUS
</string>
<string name="purchase_not_sup_title">Purchase Not Supported</string>
<string name="purchase_not_sup_msg">
In-app sales of Finney (thousandth\'s of an Ether) is not supported in this version of Uncle Finney\'s Poker.
However Uncle Finney\'s Poker contains a general-purpose Ether Wallet (Send-or-Receive-Finney). You can purchase
Ether from a cryptocurrency exchange, such as coinbase.com; Then you can transfer Ether into your Ether Wallet.
Simply go to Send-or-Receive-Finney, and select RECEIVE. Then use the SHARE button to send your wallet address
to yourself, for example via email. When you transfer Ether to that address it will appear in your Uncle Finney\'s
Poker balance.
</string>

  <!-- new-game messages -->
<string name="newgame_subtitle">Choose a Table</string>
<string name="synced_with_blockchain">synced with blockchain</string>
<string name="transactions_maybe_pending">(un-posted transactions may still be pending)</string>
<string name="at_the_started_table">at the Starter table</string>
<string name="at_the_intermediate_table">at the Intermediate table</string>
<string name="at_the_high_roller_table">at the High-Roller table</string>
<string name="with_group"></string>
<string name="minimum_is">minimum is</string>
<string name="balance_too_low_title">Your Balance is Too Low</string>
<string name="get_more_finney">you will need to acquire more Finney before you can play</string>
<string name="go_to_a_different_table">please select a different group to play with</string>
  <string name="recent_err_wait">
An error occurred during a recent attempt to deposit funds.
\n\nTherefore please wait while your account status is refreshed and all recent payments are validated.
</string>
  <string name="fees_advisory_title">
Understand Before You Play
</string>
<string name="fees_advisory">
<![CDATA[Finney have real value!<br/><br/>
\n\n<b>IMPORTANT</b>: Every time you make a bet, Uncle Finney\'s Poker deposits the
funds into a secure 3rd-party escrow (a blockchain contract). After the game, the
contract pays the \"pot\" to the winner.<br/><br/>notes:<br/>
<b>-</b> There is a small transaction fee called \"gas,\" generally less than 1 Finney,
for every transfer. This fee is the same regardless of the size of the bet. So if you\'re
betting hundreds of Finney, then the fee is a very small percentage of the bet &#8212;
but if you\'re playing at the \"Starter Table\", with very small bets of just a few Finney,
then the transaction fee can be almost equal to the \"dust\" bets.<br/><br/>
<b>-</b> There is an \"escrow\" fee of two percent that is
decucted by the escrow contract. There is no additional \"house take.\"<br/><br/>
<b>-</b> After you complete a game, it can take several minutes for your winnings
(the \"pot\") to be deposited back into your account. Be patient. The escrow contract
will <b>ALWAYS</b> send the winnings back to the appropriate player.<br/><br/>
<b>-</b> Once you start a game, there\'s no backing out. If a player exits
the game <i>for any reason</i>, even if, for example, their phone battery dies, they
<b>forfeit the game</b>. This rule protects you from players that would shut off their
phones to try and back out of a bad hand.<br/><br/>
This message will be displayed every time you come to this page, until you un-check
the \"Show Fees Advisory\" menu item.]]>
</string>
<string name="new_game_help_title">
Choose a Group to Find an Opponent
</string>
<string name="new_game_help">
The balance displayed on this screen, when up-to-date, reflects your current balance
on the blockchain. It does not include transactions that have not yet been accepted
on the blockchain, which can take up to 5 minutes, depending on network conditions. For
this reason, the balance, even when synced with the blockchain, may not reflect winnings
from your most recent game for a few minutes.
\n\nIn Uncle-Finney\'s Poker you bet real Finney, with real players. On the
next page you\'ll see a list of players who are currently online, and available for
you to challenge to a game.
\n\nIf you choose to play with strangers, then we categorize players according to how high
they want to \"set the stakes\" in their game; For example, if you choose to play at the
\"High Roller\" table, then the ante is 625 Finney, and the maximum amount of any raise is
2500 Finney.
\n\nIf you have a group of friends who are poker enthusiasts, you can create or join your
own playing group. Then you will only be visible to your friends who enter the group\'s \"magic word.\"
\n\nIf you select to play with friends, then you and your opponent will negotiate a maximum
raise. The ante will be one quarter of the negotiated maximum raise.
\n\nIf you\'re new to the game, or if you only have a very small balance, then select the
Starter Table to just get a feel for the game. But be aware that at the starter table you\'ll be
playing for such a small amount that the transaction fees will take up a significant fraction of
any winnings.
\n\nIf you are ready for a more adventurous game, then select one of the other options
to find an opponent for some serious betting!
</string>
<string name="new_game_bal_too_low">
Your balance must be at least BAL_MULTIPLE times the maximum raise (MIN_WAGER Finney).
\n\nSince your balance is less than this amount, WHAT_TO_DO.
</string>
<string name="new_game_new_group_title">
Enter a Name for Your Group
</string>
<string name="new_game_new_group">
Enter a name or \"magic word\" for a group that you would like to create or join. On
the next page you will only see other players who have typed in the same word. You will
only be visible to players from that group.
</string>
<string name="new_game_old_group_title">
Select a Group
</string>
<string name="new_game_old_group">
Select a name or \"magic word\" for a group that you would like to join. On
the next page you will only see other players who have selected the same word. You will
only be visible to players from that group.
</string>
<string name="hand_rankings_title">
Poker Hand Rankings
</string>
<string name="hand_rankings">
  <![CDATA[
	   <u>Summary:</u><br/><br/>
	   <b>Straight Flush</b><br/>
	   <b>Four of a Kind</b><br/>
	   <b>Full House</b><br/>
	   <b>Flush</b><br/>
	   <b>Straight</b><br/>
	   <b>Three of a kind</b><br/>
	   <b>Two pair</b><br/>
	   <b>One pair</b><br/>
	   <b>High card</b><br/><br/>
<u>More details:</u><br/><br/>
<b>Straight Flush</b>: Five cards in numerical order, all of identical suits.<br/><br/>
In the event of a tie: Highest rank at the top of the sequence wins. The best possible
straight flush is known as a royal flush, which consists of the ace, king, queen, jack and
ten of a suit. A royal flush is an unbeatable hand.<br/><br/>
<b>Four of a Kind</b>: Four cards of the same rank, and one side card or ‘kicker’.<br/><br/>
In the event of a tie: Highest four of a kind wins.<br/><br/>
<b>Full House</b>: Three cards of the same rank, and two cards of a different, matching rank.<br/><br/>
In the event of a tie: Highest three matching cards wins the pot.<br/><br/>
<b>Flush</b>: Five cards of the same suit.<br/><br/>
In the event of a tie: The player holding the highest ranked card wins. If necessary,
the second-highest, third-highest, fourth-highest, and fifth-highest cards can be used to break
the tie. In the rare event that all five cards are the same ranks, then we pay the Challenger.
The suit itself is never used to break a tie in poker.<br/><br/>
<b>Straight</b>: Five cards in sequence.<br/><br/>
In the event of a tie: Highest ranking card at the top of the sequence wins. Note: The Ace
may be used at the top or bottom of the sequence, and is the only card which can act in this manner.<br/><br/>
A,K,Q,J,T is the highest (Ace high) straight; 5,4,3,2,A is the lowest (Five high) straight.<br/><br/>
<b>Three of a kind</b>: Three cards of the same rank, and two unrelated side cards.<br/><br/>
In the event of a tie: Highest ranking three of a kind wins.<br/><br/>
<b>Two pair</b>: Two cards of a matching rank, another two cards of a different matching
rank, and one side card.<br/><br/>
In the event of a tie: Highest pair wins. If players have the same highest pair, highest
second pair wins. If both players have two identical pairs, highest side card wins.<br/><br/>
<b>One pair</b>: Two cards of a matching rank, and three unrelated side cards.<br/><br/>
In the event of a tie: Highest pair wins. If players have the same pair, the highest side
card wins, and if necessary, the second-highest and third-highest side card can be used to break
the tie.<br/><br/>
<b>High card</b>: Any hand that does not qualify under a category listed above.<br/><br/>
In the event of a tie: Highest card wins, and if necessary, the second-highest, third-highest,
fourth-highest and smallest card can be used to break the tie.]]>
</string>
<string name="select_opponent_help_wager_range">
On this page you can select an opponent to challenge to a poker game. You are
playing PLAYING_MSG, and you can negotiate a \"maximum raise\" from MIN_WAGER to MAX_WAGER.
The initial ante is fixed at one quarter of the maximum raise.
\n\nYou will not be able to propose or accept a game in which your balance is less than
five times the maximum raise.
</string>
<string name="select_opponent_help_fixed_wager">
On this page you can select an opponent to challenge to a poker game. You are
playing PLAYING_MSG, with a fixed maximum raise of WAGER. The initial ante is one quarter of
the maximum raise.
</string>
<string name="no_opponents_online_title">
No Opponents are Online
</string>
<string name="no_opponents_online">
You are playing PLAY_GROUP_PHRASE.
\n\nEither there are no other opponents from this group online at this moment, or all online
opponents from this group are currently engaged in games.
\n\nYou can wait here until another player comes online, or until a currently-engaged player
completes his game, or you can click CANCEL to go back and select a different group.
</string>
<string name="wallet_help_title">
Uncle Finney\'s Poker -- Ether Wallet
</string>
<string name="wallet_help">
It turns out that Finney are actually a denomination of the popular crypto-currency,
Ether &#8212; One thousand Finney\'s make one Ether. And this wallet is
actually a complete Ether wallet.
\n\nWhen you registered your Uncle Finney\'s Poker username, you created an Ether account,
which you can access here. You can check the balance of your Ether account; or send or receive
Finney (Ether) to/from other Ether addresses. You can also check the transaction history
associated with your account.
</string>  
<!-- this is not used -->
<string name="import_acct_help">
If you like you can import an Ether account that you have created with some other Ether
client &#8212; For example, I recommend https://www.myetherwallet.com/ to create Ether
wallets. Even of you already have a wallet, in order to import it you\'ll need to get the
private key, which you can do at myetherwallet.com, (under the view wallet info tab). Once
you have the private key, to import it into the EtherPay app select the \"import account\"
menu item.
\n\nNOTE: Uncle Finney\'s Poker is *not* an \"Ethereum node\"&#8212;it uses etherchain.org
to check your Ether balance; it uses your private key to sign transactions; and it uses
etherscan.io to broadcast signed transactions. Of course, your private key is never
transmitted.
</string>
<string name="about_ufp">
Uncle Finney\'s Poker Version VERSION
\n\nCredits
\n\nUncle Finney\'s Poker is built on the work of countless individuals who have made
the Ethereum platform easy to work with. Also thanks to so many who have published open
source code forming the foundation of much of the functionality of Uncle Finney\'s Poker.
Special thanks to:
\n\nEtherchain.org
\n\nEtherscan.io (Powered by Etherscan.io APIs)
\n\nethereumJS, by the Ethereum Javascript Community
\n\nZBar and the ZBar android SDK by Jeff Brown
\n\nRoberto Tyley for his SpongyCastle java repackage of the BouncyCastle crypto lib by the
Legion of the Bouncy Castle
\n\nKen Gullaksen for his QRCode generator, built on ZXing
\n\nJames Simpson and GoldFire Studios, Inc. for PokerSolver
\n\nPunjabi Graphics
\n\n\nIt is our fervent wish that this program leads to increased ownership and use of
Ether. Also we encourage others to create applications (hopefully in the same spirit of
promoting the mass-adoption of Ether), building upon and learning from our code base, much
as we have built this program building upon the work of others.
\nTherefore&#8230;
\n\nPermission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software
and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal in the Software without restriction,
including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute,
sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:
\n\nThe above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or
substantial portions of the Software.
\n\nTHE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING
BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND
NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM,
DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.
</string>
<string name="export_acct_prompt">
This QR Code represents the private key to your account. You can scan the QR Code into an
Ether wallet, or into another smart-phone that is running Uncle Finney\'s Poker. You would
do this to move your account to a different wallet. Also you can send the key to yourself
to back it up, for example, to protect your account in case you break your phone.
\n\nImportant: Do not share your private key. If you give someone your private key
then they have access to ALL the funds in your account!
\n\nNote: It is not recommended to play Uncle Finney\'s Poker from two different
devices, using the same Ether account.
</string>
<string name="receive_qr_prompt">
This QR code represents your public account address. You need to provide this address to
any  person, in order for them to send you Ether. You can allow people to scan the address
directly from your phone, or you can share it, using the share button below.
\n\nNote: It generally takes about 15 seconds for an Ether transaction to affect your
balance.
</string>
<string name="send_help_title">
Sending Ether Payments
</string>
<string name="send_help">
On this screen you can make a Finney (or Ether) payment; that is, send Finney (Ether) to the
selected address.
\n\nBefore you click the \"Pay\" button, enter the amount that you would like to send. You
Can choose to denominate the amount in either Finney or ETH.
\n\nIn the options menu you can check \"Show Data\." This will give you the ability to attach a
short note to the payment. This note will be permanently attached to the payment, and publicly
visible. For example, if you are paying a bill at a restaurant, you might enter your table number
here.
\n\nIn the options menu you can also check \"Show GAS\." Each Ether transaction includes a small
fee called \"GAS\", which pays for the computational cost of executing the transaction on the
Ethereum Virtual Machine. Gas is not denominated in Ether; to find the actual cost of a transaction
in Ether, the gas is multiplied by a gas-price, which is set by the Ethereum nodes. (The gas price
is very small, at the time of this writing appoximently 0.00000002 ETH/GAS).. Note that the
transaction only specifies the maximum gas that can be consumed; any gas that is not used is not
deducted from your account.
\n\nThe simple Payment screen gives you the ability to send Ether to simple Ether addresses &#8212;
and it sets the gas limit to a reasonable, conservative value. But in some cases you might want to
send Ether to Ether Contracts, which might require much more processing. For those cases you should
enable \"Show Gas\" in the options menu. Then you can specify the maximum gas for your transaction.
</string>
<string name="size_help_title">
Specifiy an Amount
</string>
<string name="size_help">
Use this field to specify the amount of Finney (Ether) that you would like to send. You can
denominate the amount in either Finney or ETH: One ETH is one thousand Finney.
\n\nNote: In addition to the amount you send, a small transaction fee, approximately equal to
1 Finney, will be dedcuted from your account.
</string>
<string name="gas_help_title">
About GAS
</string>
<string name="gas_help">
Use this field to specify the maximum gas that can be consumed by this transaction. For example,
for a transfer to a simple Ether account I recommend a gas-limit of 35,000 GAS. Typically the
transaction will consume less &#8212; about 21,000 GAS&#8230; A transaction to a Contract address might
consume much more. For example, vDice.io recommends a gas limit of 180,000 GAS in order to send
a payment to one of their betting contracts.
</string>
<string name="data_help_title">
Adding Data to an Ether Payment
</string>
<string name="data_help">
Use this field to attach identifying information to this payment. For example, if you are
paying a bill at a restaurant, you might enter your table number here.
</string>
  <string name="transaction_sent">
Transaction Sent
</string>
<string name="retrieving_transactions">retrieving transactions</string>
<string name="Payments_Sent">Payments Sent</string>
<string name="Payments_Received">Payments Received</string>
<string name="error_retrieving_transactions">error retrieving transactions!</string>
<string name="retrieving_X_transactions">retrieving X transactions...</string>
<string name="play_for_practice">Starter Table\n(Max. Raise WAGER)</string>
<string name="play_for_real">Intermediate Table\n(Max. Raise WAGER)</string>
<string name="play_with_pros">High Roller Table\n(Max. Raise WAGER)</string>

<string name="find_an_opponent">Find an Opponent</string>
<string name="looking_for_players">looking for players&#8230;</string>

<!--
these are the messages that preceed the beginning of a game
-->
<string name="You_Are_Challenged">You Are Challenged!</string>
<string name="decline_challenge">Decline the Challenge</string>
<string name="accept_but_new_wager">Accept but propose new wager</string>
<string name="Has_Countered">Has Countered</string>
<string name="Has_Chickened_Out">Has Chickened Out!</string>
<string name="Declined_Your_Challenge">Declined Your Challlenge</string>
<string name="ask_wager_title">How Much Are You Prepared to Wager?</string>
<string name="You_are_playing">You are playing</string>
<string name="The_minimum_wager_is">The minimum wager is</string>
<string name="the_maximum_wager_is">the maximum wager is</string>
<string name="but_cuz_your_bal_is_only">However, because your balance is only</string>
<string name="now_max_wager_is">right now the maximum wager that you can play with is</string>
<string name="enter_raise_prompt">Enter Max Raise</string>
<string name="Waiting_for_Response_from">Waiting for Response from</string>



<string name="you_are_challenged_fixed_wager">
CHALLENGER challenges you to a game!
\n\nThe maximum raise is WAGER Finney.
\n\nYou can
\n1) decline the challenge
\n3) accept the challenge
</string>
<string name="you_are_challenged">
CHALLENGER challenges you to a game!
\n\nThe proposed maximum raise is WAGER Finney.
\n\nYou can
\n1) decline the challenge;
\n2) accept the challenge, but propose a different maximum raise; or
\n3) accept the challenge and the maximum raise.
</string>
<string name="counter_wager">
CHALLENGER has countered.
\n\nThe proposed maximum raise is WAGER Finney.
\n\nYou can
\n1) decline the challenge;
\n2) accept the challenge, but propose a different maximum raise; or
\n3) accept the challenge and the maximum raise.
</string>
  <string name="no_opponents">
No opponents online: you are the first!
</string>
  <string name="wait_or_cancel">
You are waiting for CHALLENGER to answer your current challenge.
\n\nPress OK to continue waiting, or
\n\nPress Cancel to withdraw the challenge.
</string>
<string name="opponent_backed_out">
CHALLENGER has backed out of the contest (chiiiken!)&#8230; if you have already
placed a wager, then the funds will automatically be returned to your account within
a minute or two.
</string>
<string name="waiting_for_challenger">
Waiting for CHALLENGER to click OK&#8230;
</string>
<string name="payout_advisory_title">
Where\'s My Money?
</string>
<string name="payout_advisory_msg">
  <![CDATA[
Starting<br/>
balance:&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;START_BAL Finney<br/>
Your<br/>
bet(s):&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;(TX_TOTAL) Finney<br/>
Fees for TX_CNT<br/>
bet(s):&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;(TX_FEES) Finney<br/>
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;_______________<br/>
Interim<br/>
balance:&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;DEDUCTED_BAL Finney<br/>
Winnings:&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;POT Finney<br/>
Escrow fee:&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;(ESCROW_FEE) Finney<br/>
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;_______________<br/>
Final (estimated)<br/>
balance:&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;FINAL_BAL Finney<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
When your account is up-to-date with respect to all of the deductions listed above you can
expect to see a balance of approximately DEDUCTED_BAL Finney (plus or minus one, due to rounding).
<br/>
<br/>
Your winnings will be credited within about two minutes <b>After</b> your account is up-to-date
vis-a-vis deductions. At that time you will be awarded POT Finney minus a 2% escrow fee. So in
about two minutes expect to see an account balance of approximately FINAL_BAL Finney  (plus or minus one,
due to rounding).<br/>
<br/>
Note:
<br/>
After each game it may take a minute or so for your account balance to reflect any bets that
you placed during the game. That is the reason that you will see a flashing message about refreshing
your account. <i>After</i> your account is up-to-date, vis-a-vis any bets tha you placed, it may take an
<i>additional</i> minute or two for the blockchain contract to award the pot to the winner.
<br/>
<br/>
<b>Be patient!</b>
<br/>
<br/>
This message will be displayed every time you win, until you un-check the \"Show Payout Advisory\" menu
item.]]>
</string>
<!--
  these are the messages displayed during a game
 -->
<string name="Depositing_ante">Depositing ante</string>
<string name="has_deposited_his_ante">has deposited his ante</string>
<string name="Place_Your_Bet">Place Your Bet!</string>
<!-- as in, Mr. X has raised you 5 Finney... -->
<string name="has_raised_you">has raised you</string>
<!-- as in, Mr. X bet 5 Finney... -->
<string name="bet">bet</string>
<string name="Your_turn">Your turn</string>
<!-- as in, Mr. X calls -->
<string name="calls">calls</string>
<string name="Place_Bet">Place Bet</string>
<string name="Placing_bet">Placing bet</string>
<string name="Betting_is_complete">Betting is complete</string>
<string name="Select_cards_to_replace">Select cards to replace</string>
<string name="waiting_for_opponent_ante">Waiting for OPPONENT\'s ante&#8230;</string>
<string name="waiting_for_opponent_bet">Waiting for OPPONENT to bet&#8230;</string>
<string name="waiting_for_opponent_discard">Waiting for OPPONENT to discard&#8230;</string>
<string name="processing_your_deposit">Processing your deposit&#8230;</string>
<string name="opponent_difficulty">OPPONENT is experiencing technical or connectivity issues; we will give him an extra SECONDS seconds</string>
<string name="processing_opponent_deposit">Processing OPPONENT\'s deposit&#8230; SECONDS seconds</string>
<string name="game_start">Game is about to start</string>
<string name="card_strings_err">error retrieving card strings!</string>
<string name="Folding">Folding</string>
<string name="you_win_title">You Win!</string>
<string name="opponent_wins_title">OPPONENT Wins</string>
<string name="abandoned_game_title">Abandoned Game</string>
<string name="You_have">You have</string>
<string name="opponent_has">OPPONENT has</string>
<string name="forfeited_the_game">forfeited the game!</string>
<string name="abandoned_msg">This game has been abandoned!</string>
<string name="forfeited_msg_prompt">Forfeit message</string>
<string name="You_win_the_pot">You win the pot!</string>
<string name="opponent_wins_the_pot">OPPONENT wins the pot. Better luck next time.</string>
<string name="exit_game_title">Exit This Game?</string>
<string name="exit_game_msg">
If you exit this game, then you forfeit, and OPPONENT will win the pot!
\n\nPress Cancel to continue the game, or Exit to exit
</string>
  <string name="bet_limited">
Your bet is limited to ensure that you have sufficient funds to call any opponent bet
</string>
  <string name="fairness_bug">
hey! encountered an anomaly in the fairness verification&#8230; SOMETHING DOES NOT SEEM RIGHT!!!
</string>
  <string name="internet_bet_err_msg">
Your Internet connection failed, and we were unable to deposit your bet.
\n\nUnfortunately, this forces you to forfeit the game. So OPPONENT_USERNAME wins.
</string>
  <string name="funds_will_be_credited">
Note: the pot will be automatically credited to your account, usually in less than two minutes.
</string>
<!--
    status and error messages
 -->
  <string name="no_internet_title">
Uh Oh: Internet Connectivity Problem
</string>
  <string name="no_internet">
\n\nUncle Finney\'s Poker requires a reliable Internet connection. Unfortunately we are
currently unable to access the Internet now.
\n\nThe specific error is:
\n\nERROR
\n\nPlease check your Internet connection
</string>
  <string name="partner_sites_title">
Error Accessing Blockchain
</string>
  <string name="partner_sites">
Uncle Finney\'s Poker needs to retrieve real-time information from several website
services, including:
\n\nEtherchain.org
\n\nEtherscan.io
\n\nUnfortunately, at the moment, one or both of these services seems to be non-functional.
Please try again after these services return to their normal, excellent function.
\n\nThe specific error is:
\n\nERROR\n
</string>
  <string name="partner_sites_w_retry">
Uncle Finney\'s Poker needs to retrieve real-time information from several website
services, including:
\n\nEtherchain.org
\n\nEtherscan.io
\n\nUnfortunately, either one or both of these services is experiencing some \"hiccups\", or perhaps your
Internet connection introduced significant latency in retrieving data from these sites. The specific error is:
\n\nERROR\n
\nIf this was a one-time occurrence, you can choose to try again; or you can exit the program and try
again after your Internet connection becomes more reliable and/or these services return to their
normal, excellent function.
</string>
  <string name="error_check_connection">
Network error. Please check your internet connection.
</string>
  <string name="dns_exception">
DNS Lookup Timeout or Exception
</string>
  <string name="socket_exception">
Socket Timeout Exception
</string>
  <string name="game_server_comm_fail">
communication with game server failed
</string>
  <string name="failed_to_register">
failed to register with game server
</string>
    <string name="wait_frefresh_bal">
please wait... still refreshing account balance...
</string>
  <string name="acct_up_to_date">
account status is up-to-date
</string>
  <string name="bad_private_key">
invalid private key; length is
</string>
  <string name="bad_acct_from_key">
invalid account address from key; length is
</string>
  <string name="new_acct_success">
new acct sucessfully imported:
</string>
  <string name="cant_read_balance">
unable to retrieve your balance
</string>
    <string name="del_acct_question">
Delete current account?
</string>
  <string name="partner_sites_down">
Partner sites are down!
</string>
  <string name="network_err">
Network error. Please check your internet connection
</string>
  <string name="uhoh_connectivity_title">
  Uh Oh: Internet Connectivity Problem
</string>
  <string name="uhoh_connectivity_balance_msg">
Your Internet connection failed, and we were unable to retrieve your actual balance.
\n\nPlease check your Internet connection
  </string>
  <string name="block_nos_err">
unable to read block numbers from etherscan.io or etherchain.org
</string>
  <string name="cant_reg_wo_device_id">
We cannot register you as a player without your unique device id
</string>
  <string name="contacting_server">
Contacting game server...
</string>
  <string name="login_err">
login error
</string>
  <string name="err_getting_opponent_list">
error retrieving opponent list!
</string>
  <string name="Error">
Error
</string>
  <string name="tx_err_ok">
An error occurred while attempting this transaction -- press OK to continue
</string>
  <string name="tx_success_ok">
your transaction was sent successfully -- press OK to continue
</string>
  <string name="cant_send_zero">
Cannot send zero Finney/ETH
</string>
  <string name="parse_gas_limit">
Unable to parse Gas limit
</string>
  <string name="gas_too_low">
Gas limit is too low -- transaction might not succeed!
</string>
  <string name="not_sufficient_to_cover">
is not sufficient to cover
</string>
  <string name="recipient_invalid_length_is">
Recipient address is not valid; length is
</string>
  <string name="recipient_invalid_own">
Recipient cannot be the same as your account address
</string>
  <string name="for_price">for</string>
  <string name="plus">plus</string>
  <string name="Balance">Balance</string>
  <string name="processing">processing</string>
  <string name="Accept">Accept</string>
  <string name="Continue">Continue</string>
  <string name="Cancel">Cancel</string>
  <string name="About">About</string>
  <string name="Done">Done</string>
  <string name="Call">Call</string>
  <string name="Check">Check</string>
  <string name="No_bet">No bet</string>
  <string name="TRY_AGAIN">TRY AGAIN</string>
  <string name="EXIT">EXIT</string>
  <string name="Exit">Exit</string>
  <string name="OK">OK</string>

</resources>
